softinterface.com 2018-12-31

# Softinterface Privacy Policy Explained in detail.

We respect the privacy of our visitors. We are gravely concerned about practices which violate the basic rights of choice and confidentiality. 

Here is our covenant with those readers who trust us with their personal information.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.Softinterface.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:

  * What information we collect
  * With whom it is shared
  * How it can be corrected
  * How it is secured
  * How policy changes will be communicated
  * How to address concerns over misuse of personal data

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order. We will **never** give, lease or sell your e-mail or any other information, period. We DO NOT sell OR exchange advertising space in our e-mail publications to other companies, we do not allow third parties any other use of our lists. We will never expose your name, nor e-mail address to anyone outside SoftInterface.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

NOTE:  This site does not collect financial information such as credit card numbers. Rather that information is collected by the secure PayPal servers. PayPal uses encryption methods to protect this information. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

#### Your Access to and Control Over Information   

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at via the email address or phone number provided on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any
  * Change/correct any data we have about you
  * Have us delete any data we have about you
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

#### Policy for Minors

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to non-adults (under the age of 18). If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

#### Security 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as billing and shipping address), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Notification of Changes

You may check this URL for policy changes going forward.

If you feel for any reason that your information has been compromised. Please contact Softinterface, personally, at:  

**Last Modified Date: 5/12/2018**
